Helped me with this as well.
I actually implemented the step by step
grooming with the agent.
I will try to generate an MD file you can
use with this type of structure.
So you can start describing things on
your own and and also answer questions
for the for the agent.
You won't be able to implement anything
here,
but you will have a better answers than
Right.
me because I am taking my information
from what I know from.
And from, excuse me,
from our grooming sessions.
Actually I am also putting the grooming
sessions I have with David that he also
Correct.
gave me some feedback. Mm-hmm.
Right.
And yeah, let's go with this.
I think it's this one. Sorry,
it's the one.
In this case, yeah,
so let's go step by step this, this.
Sorry, done.
OK, so we have this three,
six points that we have already done.
Let's go with the big one, the AR and PR.
So if I select here.
This is our orders, right?
So this shipment has two orders, right?
So if I go to.
I should that's two orders, correct? Yeah.
Yeah, if I go to cost allocation here,
I have the tab. Well, this doesn't matter.
This is the same thing.
But now we are not showing every single
order from the other row rows here.
I'm sorry, let me open this. Yeah.
Because before we were showing the orders
of all of them,
but we we just want to know about the
orders of the selected one, right?
Correct.
OK.
And then that is the one of the points I
think.
Oh, sorry. Um.
So this is the summary and we have that.
We have just four orders showing up.
Four orders if you go back,
if you if if you go, I go up.
I did.
Yeah, well that.
If you go up to the line line or the
table, right?
Uh-huh. The line of the table,
the this one.
Yeah, yeah, here. OK.
You have four orders and if you hover
Huh.
over that, you hover,
hover over the order number, right. Oh,
Huh.
OK. OK. So you have two M1M7M and OM.
OK OM 7M. Fantastic. Yeah,
that's what it is.
We need so much, right? OK.
Yeah, yeah. It's all matches.
Direct cost is this much. OK.
Yeah.
The base rate is this 10. OK.
It is across this fuel charge is 382. OK,
stop of charge.
But why the stop off charge is only you
have different values in different lines?
OK.
Oh, OK, OK. But no,
it should not be in different orders,
Um.
right?
Yeah,
well they there are four orders in the
shipment and I this is what I have and
this is the AAAP, right?
AP Yeah, yeah, that is AR correct.
But AR you will you will creating. OK,
And this is the A.
OK.
OK, mhm.
that's fine. Yeah,
we will have the AR as well.
If you go to AR, if you go to AR,
click on the AR.
I.
Mhm. OK.
OK,
base rate fuel and you have stop off
charges and uh.
You have the margin as well, right?
So you on the top you have margin that is
31%. Yeah, his total is uh.
Uh, a moment.
Why?
Why you are having total less if you if
you go back one second.
OK, give me, give me one second, Jenna.
I need to give me one minute, yes.
Yeah.
OK.
Hey, I'm so sorry about that. Um.
No problem. Yeah.
OK, uh, you were saying about AR?
Yeah.
If you go to AR,
when you say this base right, it is 1429.
Mhm.
But if you look at the AR total,
why is it summing everything up and
Mhm.
saying it is 8134?
Oh, sorry, why this is showing up? OK.
This one, right? Sorry, this one.
Yeah, it should be. It should be 2033,
right? Yeah, total.
Because it's the it's the summer.
They are really. Oh yeah, that's right.
This is bad.
This is not matching this one and but
this is.
Yeah, so it should be.
Correct.
It should be to this one and it is if
So this.
Mhm.
distribution.
If you see here the base base 142914K14
OK.
Yeah, the AR total.
And if you look at the base,
all the base might not be 1429, right?
It's a distribution of that.
Yeah, sure.
Total value, right? The base,
say for example base was 1000, right?
Mhm.
The first order might have 300,
the 2nd order might have 400, right?
Then 100 hundred, right?
Something like that.
So that the base is distributed equally,
not equally,
Mhm.
but distributed across these four orders.
Similarly,
fuel similarly stop off and when you get
OK.
the AR total,
you get the AR total as 2033.
OK.
And then this is the will be the total,
the big, the big total right then?
Yeah,
you can leave it as that total and then
you could just give the breakdown
breakdown here.
OK, very good. OK.
And then so you're telling me the base is?
The sum of everything here or is like
different number? It's it's different,
No, base is base is separate.
Fuel is separate. Discount is separate.
right?
OK.
Stop off charges are separate.
Stop off charges are separate, right?
Whatever you are adding,
you keep on adding to the right.
OK.
Say there could be many additional
charges.
Right. Say for example,
if you needed a driver help at load for
loading,
then it could be a charge for that
particular this one. That's fine, right?
So similarly you can have additional
OK.
services.
Hmm.
OK, so because here I put the AR of this,
the order total of this AR and this is
Correct.
the global total.
Yeah, correct.
It will be sum of all that sum of all the
line order one, order two,
order three and order 4.
OK,
then I just need to shuffle the the
values my database didn't recognize.
I think the that needs to be different,
Correct. Correct. Yeah, yeah, right.
If you do that, that should be fine.
no problem.
If similar thing for the AP as well.
OK. And now I did this. Yeah, go ahead.
Sorry.
Right, so you.
Yeah,
for AP you see you have direct cause,
that's fine.
So similarly for the base you did 1091
Huh.
across all, right?
It won't be 1091 across all.
OK.
It'll be break up just like how we talked
about the total is 1552.
Yeah.
And for 1552,
how do you want to split it between these
orders?
You can randomly put some numbers and
Yeah.
then so that it matches so that you get
the first line would be.
AP total would be the total of the 1st
order,
Mm.
AP total will be the total of the 2nd
order, but if you sum it up it should be.
Yeah.
Uh 1552.
Sure. OK.
And obviously we need different values,
so it's more realistic, right? OK, OK,
so here I made a model to here I made a
Yeah, correct.
like a a small mistake.
I I will fix it right away.
Like I I separated both because
previously I had a lot of orders, right?
Because he was listing all of the orders.
So I didn't realize that was we're not
Mhm.
going to have a space to put both side by
side. That's that was my first intention.
This is why I did this.
But now we have a space because like we
are just showing the orders of the
shipment. So we can put it here,
Correct.
down here and we can remove this API in R
and we don't need to have this too
because I did this. I did this also.
Oh.
OK.
Mhm.
Uh 00M.
Oh, it is for the first order.
Oh, yeah, we need. Yeah,
we need to change it for two different
orders, right? Sure. OK.
Yeah, OK.
But I would say instead of you don't need
this, right? Do you need this?
No, I mean my concern was that compare it.
Or you can, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You then then you can see if you put it
right,
then you put order drop down so that you
can change between different orders.
No, no. Here you you click on that,
you click on that,
Yeah, sure. Yeah, right.
then you have the order number, right?
So you put a drop down there so that you
can change to different orders because
there are four orders.
Huh.
So the values are going to change for
each of those orders.
OK, perfect.
So you can compare between AP and AR for
each of those orders.
OK. Yeah, that sounds good.
I need to do that.
Bye.
OK.
Or we can even we can actually put tabs
maybe because since we just we have a
five order limits per shipment,
I think you can fit a tab tabs here.
I will see.
Yeah, yeah.
You can do that and you can get the
Um.
margin because you have for the overall,
you have the margin on the top, right.
OK, mhm.
If you close this for the entire AP and
the AR, you have the margin on the top,
right. So that takes care of, yeah,
so that takes care.
Yeah.
But if someone wants to see individual
margin and compare.
Them then this is a good screen right to
compare and see.
Mhm.
OK, erfect. I like this. OK,
now it's clear.
Yeah, yeah, that's good. Yeah.
Let's go wait.
So Caitlin was making me do this thing.
It doesn't.
It doesn't like relate to our thing,
but look at it.
She wants to create the landing page from.
Who's this?
Kathleen.
Oh, Kathleen. OK, OK,
the future of logistics is loading.
Yeah.
What is this?
So she she wanted me to do a landing page
for like marketing and this is one of the
versions.
Oh, OK. OK.
And I will show you later the other ones,
but it's that that's why it's here.
Um, OK, let's go with the next one.
Which one is this?
Tap reorder. OK, the tap reorder.
I made it. So we have order first,
product stops, routing guide,
cost allocation, instructions, documents,
notes and so on. Is that OK?
Correct.
And then there is the control button
right to change the reorder.
Yeah, exactly this one.
I need to still fail it.
Yeah.
OK then product stop default explained.
Product stop.
Oh yeah,
this is David told me this should be
shown like because it is collapsed, right?
And we should show it all like expanded
Yeah.
so the user can see.
Yeah, starting, starting,
you show expanded,
then afterwards you leave them with
different minor signs so that you know
Uh.
they can close and see only the ones that
they wanted. But when when it opens,
keep it all open.
At.
Yeah, it is working that now uh that way.
No, no. If you go back,
if you go back to the product,
Yeah.
there are four orders.
How do I see four orders? OK, 00107, OK,
So.
yeah, yeah, yeah, 791 and 26, OK.
And their first line,
see what I was asking was.
That minus sign should be for the 1st
order. Oh, OK, OK.
Uh.
And then you don't have anything,
no other line. So you left it like that,
right? OK, so there was nothing.
But is there a differentiation that you
Right.
can bring in so that it clearly sees that?
OK, this is.
As all the information related to the
order,
this is all say can you have say for the
first line right you have ORD 00 #2,
can you introduce that before order two?
Similarly, order three, order four.
Instead of two, it will have one.
Mm.
So it clearly differentiates saying that
OK,
Yeah, sure.
this is order what the 1st order related
lines, the 2nd order related lines,
Oh.
3rd order related lines,
4th order related lines, right?
Exactly. OK, that makes sense actually.
Do not have to add a repeated name here,
right?
Also also don't have a repeated name here,
What is it?
right?
Because we're only showing this one here.
Yeah, you don't have to repeat it. Yeah,
you don't have to repeat it.
You could just say,
you know that you tell that and then you
1-2, right?
And then you have the next order, right?
Mhm.
Exactly.
You don't have to repeat it in the second
and the third line.
Yeah, perfect. That that way we will,
we will user will understand also that is
that this one's belong to this one
because of this space. OK,
Correct. Exactly.
that's good then.
Yeah, one one second.
If you go back to the product, right,
Yeah.
and if you go to the right,
there is a setting here, right?
Adjust the columns.
Do you have that column adjustment for me?
Big columns no I need I need to like
fulfill the all of these things otherwise
I don't know the scope of this.
I know how it how it should work but I
don't I don't want to like have too many
issues later so I'm I'm just saving this
for for the last part.
OK, OK, OK, OK.
When we don't worry,
it won't be done quick. Uh.
See,
even if you if you don't have exact
information,
you just put some like two or three
information so that to just give them
idea, right?
This is more about giving idea, yeah.
Yeah, the idea exactly.
And also as you as I understand you told
me that these the business people.
Are checking values,
so it needs to make sense as well.
It's not like whatever.
Yeah, if you are picking the four,
four orders because we picked the four
orders in that particular line.
So it should be 4 orders below.
That's all right.
They're not going to look into the data
Hm.
of what it is and all those things like
say for example,
they're not going to look into your
shipment, shipment ID, right, ship item.
Mhm.
Like you can put any ship item,
that's fine, right?
Mhm.
So but it is just to give some idea about
it.
OK, good.
And so we are we are in the products. OK,
export the model,
all columns then this export one.
So how does it look guys?
Yeah, 200 records, export all columns,
export, uh, visible columns. Yeah,
that's it.
Right. And you have 10,000 records. OK,
yeah, fine, 200.
We can do.
So you have 200 records there if you
close this one.
Yeah.
Yeah, we have. This is counting.
I can add more if you like.
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, that's fine. Yeah.
And and we actually have a database with
200, you know,
just so we are flexible in adding more if
you like. Here is working as well.
Yeah.
If you can see it,
it's downloading the CSB.
So maybe the businessman want to want to
see the here.
I think this one has the all of the all
of the columns.
And then?
This one only divisible.
Correct. Only visible columns. Yeah,
that's it. That's cool.
You already implemented some of those.
There you go. Yeah, exactly. You know,
I know this is taking a little bit longer
than expected and due to the meeting that
we have this morning with Laurie,
Yeah.
but I know like,
but it will be very useful for when when
we are already done with this.
Yeah.
Like the people that needs to review it,
it's going to have a lot of clarity and
Correct.
also this will serve as a documentation
for development.
So we are like actually taking further
steps.
Yeah.
So everything that we have delayed now we
we're going to compensate later because
this is really.
Robust.
Yeah.
Sound down.
But anyway, we are, we are,
we are trying this one out.
It really works out well.
Then everyone likes it.
Then we can implement it across, right?
So.
Yeah, sure. And then document types.
We removed invoice instructions, order,
added POD. Let's go to document types.
Oh.
Here.
Mm.
I think documents were OK, right?
So we talked about it last time in voice
instruction. Upload attachments, right?
Upload.
Uh huh.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah, this one. I'm sorry.
Let me let me open this.
I need to fix it here.
I think this is what I think this is what
David told me.
Let me let me give a a note here.
He told me this document type should be.
Probe of delivery SL shipping list.
Packaging O here I.
Packaging list, yeah.
So here are they. Uh, all of them.
Yeah, shipping list. Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah. Others.
OK.
You just leave others so that they would
be able to attach emails as well.
e-mail communications, anything else,
right? Something. Yeah,
Oh, OK.
they just leave others as well so that
you can put.
Yeah.
OK.
A picture.
Say for example they have said they have
OK.
Uhhuh.
sent a picture like do not something,
something they need to, you know,
a picture of something,
a package or something that needs to be
handled properly so they can send it and
then you know you can attach that as well
Uh huh.
for reference.
OK, perfect. Makes sense.
Are these gonna be validated though?
What do you mean by validated?
There's nothing to validate that.
Like if.
It is just an attachment so that the user
can see those right?
OK.
There is no validation for it.
Because if we.
OK, because these are like Excel files,
right? CSV files.
It could be Excel, it could be PDF.
Oh, OK. It could be anything.
So you don't need validation then. OK.
Yeah, right. It could be image.
Like JPEG something.
Also let me fail this part with as if we
are are uploading a lot of other things
Right, right. Yeah.
here so that people can see.
And do you have a preview preview of the
document or just like it downloads
automatically? If you click on the file,
you have PDF, right?
So what happens if you click on the file?
It opens.
Yeah.
Oh no,
I can create one though I can create.
No, no, no. I'm just asking,
it downloads or it opens or gives you a
OK.
preview. What happens?
It is supposed to be showing a preview
that will that will make more sense.
Yeah, if you if you can create a preview,
that is nice, right?
You can just create a preview and then
put a button there to download it because
OK.
you don't want them to download it and
then see open and see what it is, right?
Mhm.
Give them a preview of what it is,
just like how in Outlook.
You can click on the attachment and then
take a preview before you even you can
Huh.
download it.
OK, that will be nice. Yeah.
Yeah.
And this one can delete it. OK then.
And then you have options to delete it.
Can you go back?
Yeah, I I can.
Let's let's try with another one then.
If we go here, here I have see.
Uh, OK, you can delete. OK, cool.
That's it.
OK, cool.
I will fill it more so you can in in the
demo you can like click.
Mm.
Then the next one is vendor status names.
Which is tender history and history,
right?
Yeah, tender history, history.
History is regular history, right?
Send request.
History is like what changes that
happened when we talked about it, right?
Mhm.
Right. Say for example,
a shipment update happened,
you add an update and then.
You know, you make a note of it.
This is what a shipment update happened.
The order update happened, right?
Mm-hmm. OK, I would like to know.
That is what is going to be as part of
the history, right? Tender history.
You can leave it blank. For now,
we don't have to do it.
OK, did 10.
OK,
I think this was refers to other thing.
I did cancel. Oh yeah, I remember this.
It was I think here this one. Yeah,
you told me we need to have it like
accepted, declined, pending, declined.
Correct, correct.
Do you? Do you remember? Yeah.
So we we actually.
Yeah, and and the other one,
instead of like calling it routing guide,
it should be tendering, right?
If you remember,
we talked about it the other screen,
the attachments, right? For example,
Um.
the PPD that I sent you the second one,
that's what it needs to be here.
Huh.
OK, OK, great. Uh, so.
Right. Instead of routing guide,
it needs to be tender.
Mhm.
OK, so it will be called tender.
Yeah, the one that I sent you, right?
The PPD 2.
OK.
Mm-hmm. Give me a second. I will.
I will open it.
Finder.
OK.
So it was.
OK. Um,
do you mean this one or is the other one
I think?
Yeah, this one, correct.
This is what needs to come there.
OK.
Right,
so the same screen will be applicable in
planning monitoring as well.
So once you put this one,
the same screen will be available in
planning exceptions and planning
monitoring right?
Both the the same screen tender screen
OK.
will be there because all screens are
same across these two.
Tabs right that leads these two metrics.
OK.
Are you getting it?
OK.
Like let me show you the the the one that
I have right now it's like this, right?
Yeah.
And we have the statuses and then give me
a second.
Um.
Yeah, you're referring to this part,
right? Also.
Uh.
Could you?
What do you mean by referring to this
part? I didn't get your point.
Because right now we have it like this,
right?
And I feel it's something is missing here
from this part.
Correct.
Right. It needs to be like this,
correct the from the shipment order,
Huh.
initial pickup,
final delivery action buttons,
everything should be there that.
OK, so it's the same thing, right?
Because on your your initial.
It is. It is the same thing.
What I'm trying to tell you is, yeah,
what I'm trying to say tell you is if you
look at the top right,
you have a planning exception and
planning monitoring right.
Uh.
Both screens have the same information.
You put it as the same information exit.
OK.
Oh.
Right.
So most of the places we don't have to,
you know,
we we won't be able to exactly tell the
user how it works, right?
But we can give them the idea.
So keep the same image on the planning
exceptions and planning monitoring.
In the planning exceptions in the
planning. OK, yes. Um.
I got you like they they think I am. I am.
I have doubts.
Right? Yeah.
It's like where do you like?
Give me a second because this one looks
to me that this is an overview right
before seeing the table.
And yeah,
you can say that this is a summary and
the below is more details.
Mm-hmm.
But here and I'm sorry if I if I'm mixing
things,
but here I think that that is different.
It is different. That's what I'm saying.
This needs to come there and the name
But.
needs to be changed to from routing guide
to tender.
OK.
OK, yeah, this is. So you're saying this,
this one is the same for this other one,
so I can use it. I can reuse it there,
right? OK.
Correct, correct, correct.
OK, cool. Um.
But you need to change the name from
routing guide to tender.
Uh, yeah. So it's gonna be,
it's gonna be named tender for here and
Yeah. No, no, no.
Everywhere it is going to be tender.
from here it's gonna be routing guide,
right?
Change the name to tender. Yeah.
Everyone is gonna be tender. OK, OK,
now I got you.
I think that that's it for now.
Let me just,
I was finishing the other ones that are
still on the works.
So can we can we have a call later so I
can explain you wanted me to ask you ask
me something before?
Right.
Correct. Correct. Yeah.
Tell me.
And one second, if you go back,
go back to your.
Design. Yeah. And for history, right?
If you go to history, the last tab, right,
Mhm.
OK.
can you add? We talked about Jira, right?
Jira, how it has information, right?
OK.
Will you be able to add some examples,
say like user name?
And date and time.
What changed order update right?
Something I I put that information in the
PowerPoint as well, right?
Oh.
Examples of how it would needs to get
updated or displayed.
Can you will you be able to update that
as well?
Uh, yes, sure. Of course I will. Um,
I think we talked about that last last
time, right as well.
Correct. Yeah,
we did talk about that last time, right.
Now this is changed.
Whenever, yeah, whenever you get that,
I think rest of the ones looks OK,
only the tender screen.
If you are not ready with the tender
screen, we can still, as David said,
right,
we can go with this information first.
Huh.
And review with them.
Okay, that's good. Yeah.
Yeah,
so we can give them some idea about how
it would look and then if you go to the
top it will be monitoring PGIPGR, right?
Mhm.
My only question is say for example if
the user would want to see.
To all of these,
they should be able to query.
Do you have the same searches as well?
Saved searches. You have saved searches.
Save searches. Yeah, sure.
This one is part. Yeah, those are queries.
Right. Save searches. OK, OK,
then you click on it.
Does it update update something?
Mm-hmm. Here you see. Have you seen it?
OK.
Ah, OK, cool. That's cool.
Then you have everything.
I think for now it is OK, right?
It's the it's only this table that I need
to finish and then the other the other
tabs the the fixes. Yep,
and then that's it.
Yeah, and what are those three dots?
I don't know that that's something I
frame put here because like maybe
thinking that we can have some options
here, I don't know. Should we remove it?
Uh, for for actions.
What do you have under actions?
Nothing as of right now.
Do you remember we talk about this and
Yeah, we talked about it.
That's why I was wondering,
you tell me just leave it?
what is this three dots and actions are
supposed to mean, right?
Is it similar or is it different, right?
Mm.
Well, I I thought it was different.
Say yeah,
for actions you can say tender to
preferred carrier, right?
You can put 11 action as tender to
preferred carrier or you can put replan,
right? Just two examples, right?
Mhm.
Do say replan.
Or yeah,
you can have these two as an action.
OK, replan.
Right. But yeah,
replan and tender to preferred carrier.
OK,
I think this this one we already have it
here in your documentation.
It's the yeah,
it says by shipment and edit.
That was the idea initially. OK.
Correct, correct. Yeah. And yeah,
you can have by shipment dated, right.
Mhm.
And then you can have what is that tender
to preferred carrier and then third one
is replat.
Oh, it's here, right?
No, you you, you forget replan.
You don't put replan.
Replan is going to happen from this one.
What?
What do you call light enter to preferred
carrier? Yeah,
you just put these two together.
That's enough for now.
OK, this soon.
Edit Yeah,
edit by shipment and the next one is edit
Uhuh.
by shipment,
then tender to preferred carrier.
And by edit and by shipment.
Gender to prefer carrier. OK,
do we have something similar here?
Not right?
Because this is very this is different
actions here.
These are different actions, right? Yeah.
Hm.
OK.
New stops will list you the stops, right?
You already have stops if you recall,
right? You already have stop information,
correct if you select that.
Yeah.
Exactly. Let me go just stops.
Yeah, that is going to come up there,
right stops.
And here I changed the thing that you
said pick up delivery.
Yeah. Pick up daily, yeah.
OK.
OK,
it looks I I really like I I am really
enjoying this, although sometimes.
It's good. Really coming out well, right?
So yeah.
Yeah, let me let me send you this later.
So see if you can if you can use it in
copilot like it will be an empty file
with the.
With the planning mode right in it,
the same planning mode that I am using so
Yeah, right, right, right.
you can so you can do it. What else?
I think that's it.
I need to go out to lunch.
We can meet at what time do you can you
do it?
We can do it later, right?
What time you are available?
I am. Well,
I am available all the afternoon today.
I want to put my focus here so you can
maybe we can talk like at 5:30 my time.
OK.
OK, sure, sure. Yeah.
But I just wanted to clarify a few things,
Um.
right? We have probably 15 more minutes.
If you're done,
maybe just I can ask those questions,
right?
Mhm.
OK, sure. Let's clarify.
Yeah, I will stop recording here.